The Peoples of the Pirá-Paraná Collection of Stephen Hugh-Jones and Christine Hugh-Jones
Nettie Lee Benson Latin American Collection,
- Audiocassette Tapes
  - Colombia, 1991
    - [SHJ-087-A] Kahi gategü büsüse (stirring coca leaves sounds) (Box 2, Item 87)
    - [SHJ-087-A] Kahi gategü büsüse (stirring coca leaves sounds) (Box 2, Item 87)
    - [SHJ-087-A] Kahi ~boare wiihü ~yabide (coca processing at night sounds) (Box 2, Item 87)
    - [SHJ-087-A] Gawa~raka ~gaberi ~keara keti (fighting w White people story) (Box 2, Item 87)
    - [SHJ-087-A] Gawa~raka ~gaberi ~keara keti traducción (Box 2, Item 87)
    - [SHJ-087-A] ~I hakü rii~boari keti (story about his F and Rubber Gatherers) (Box 2, Item 87)
    - [SHJ-087-B] ~Kii ~boara wesehü büsüse (peeling manioc in garden sounds) (Box 2, Item 87)
    - [SHJ-087-B] ~Robia keti ~gohara wesehü (women converse while peeling manioci in garden (Box 2, Item 87)
    - [SHJ-087-B] ~Kii ~boara wesehü büsüse (peeling manioc in garden sounds) (Box 2, Item 87)
    - [SHJ-087-B] ~Kii ~boara wesehü büsüse (peeling manioc in garden sounds) (Box 2, Item 87)
    - [SHJ-087-B] ~Robia wwihü tudira wese ~boare hüdohü (women returning fr garden) (Box 2, Item 87)
    - [SHJ-087-B] Wesehü büsüse (Box 2, Item 87)
    - [SHJ-087-B] ~Baha hoa, kahi waha kütise (feather ornaments, coca as valuables) (Box 2, Item 87)
    - [SHJ-087-B] Yeba kahi keti Yeba obtains coca (fragment) (Box 2, Item 87)
    - [SHJ-087-B] Keti gotigü (talking) (Box 2, Item 87)
    - [SHJ-088-A] Ti~rübü keti (about past times) (Box 2, Item 88)
    - [SHJ-088-A] ~Bakaroka büsüse (forest sounds) (Box 2, Item 88)
    - [SHJ-088-A] ~Kobeya ~wabe kütiriahaüri (Komenya, rapids, sacred geography) (Box 2, Item 88)
    - [SHJ-088-B] Riaga büsüse (river sounds) (Box 2, Item 88)
    - [SHJ-089-A] Wurika büsüse (Pilatus porter landing/taking off) (Box 2, Item 89)
    - [SHJ-089-A] Wurika büsüse (Pilatus porter landing/taking off) (Box 2, Item 89)
    - [SHJ-089-A] Tra~ira keti (experiences in Traíra) (Box 2, Item 89)
    - [SHJ-089-A] Oro ~boara (mining sounds) (Box 2, Item 89)
    - [SHJ-089-A] Oro keti (about gold) (Box 2, Item 89)
    - [SHJ-089-A] Oro ~boara machina~raka (mining machinery sounds) (Box 2, Item 89)
  - Recoya Hido, Cano Colorado
    - [SHJ-090] ~Basa ~ida ~wabe keti (on names and naming), undated (Box 2, Item 90)
    - [SHJ-090] Guu koro, wewo (tortoise w panpipes), 1968-1971 (Box 2, Item 90)
    - [SHJ-090] ~üde ~watia basase, Hasa ~basa ye (pupunha mask songs fr. Apaporis), 1970 March 21 (Box 2, Item 90)
    - [SHJ-091] Weewo basa (Pan-pipe dance), 1968-1971 (Box 2, Item 91)
    - [SHJ-091] ~Ude ~watia basase (pupunha mask songs), 1970 March 21 (Box 2, Item 91)
    - [SHJ-092-A_tapejam] Cordoba keti (Cordoba story), 1979 (Box 2, Item 92)
    - [SHJ-093] ~Robi ~Kubu keti hüdo (Romi Kumu story contd), 1985 May 9 (Box 2, Item 93)
    - [SHJ-093] ~Robi ~Kubu keti (Romi Kumu story), 1985 May 9 (Box 2, Item 93)
    - [SHJ-094] ~Robi ~Kubu keti gaha (Romi Kumu story end), 1985 May 9 (Box 2, Item 94)
    - [SHJ-094] ~Süe ~Waribi keti (Warimi story), 1985 May 9 (Box 2, Item 94)
    - [SHJ-094] ~Süe ~Waribi keti (Warimi story), 1985 May 9 (Box 2, Item 94)
    - [SHJ-095-A] ~Süe ~Waribi keti (Warimi story), 1985 May 9 (Box 2, Item 95)
    - [SHJ-096-A] ~Wadoose Benjaminye (Preventative shamanism for Benj.), 1985 May 15 (Box 3, Item 96)
    - [SHJ-096-A] Basere goti~ra (SHJ discusses shamanism w.Pasico), 1985 May 15 (Box 3, Item 96)
    - [SHJ-096-A] ~Wadoose Esteban Elsaye (Preventative shamanism for SHJ, Elsa Gomez), 1985 May 15 (Box 3, Item 96)
    - [SHJ-097] Wahü keti (Wahü story), 1985 May (Box 3, Item 97)
    - [SHJ-097] ~Buhi hakü keti (roofing-leaf father story), 1985 May (Box 3, Item 97)
    - [SHJ-097] Wahü keti (Wahü story), 1985 May (Box 3, Item 97)
    - [SHJ-099-A] ~Yaba ~goa (deer bone flute), 1979 (Box 3, Item 99)
    - [SHJ-099-A] Sühü (snail shell ocarina), 1979 (Box 3, Item 99)
    - [SHJ-099-A] ~Yaba ~goa, Sühüre gotigu (about instruments played), 1979 (Box 3, Item 99)
    - [SHJ-099-A] Guu, Yai keti (Tortoise and Jaguar story), 1979 (Box 3, Item 99)
    - [SHJ-099-A] ~Wati biru büsüse (biru spirit whistle), 1979 (Box 3, Item 99)
    - [SHJ-099-A] Eha~rare ~sedira hee rika sooria wiihü (Greetings at fruit ritual), 1979 July 12-1979 July 13 (Box 3, Item 99)
    - [SHJ-099-A] Hee (Yurupary flutes), 1979 July 12-1979 July 13 (Box 3, Item 99)
    - [SHJ-099-A] Hee rika ~sabara (Yurupary trumpets), 1979 July 12-1979 July 13 (Box 3, Item 99)
    - [SHJ-099-A] Ehadiaha ~büa (1st chant session at Hee rika sooria wii), 1979 July 12-1979 July 13 (Box 3, Item 99)
    - [SHJ-099-B] Ehadiaha ~badi hüdo (End of Ehadiaha ~badi chant), 1979 July 12-1979 July 13 (Box 3, Item 99)
    - [SHJ-099-B] Pedro telling myth contd., 1979 (Box 3, Item 99)
    - [SHJ-099-B] Pedro telling myth contd., 1979 (Box 3, Item 99)
    - [SHJ-100-A] Hee budi~ra ~bakahü (the hee leave the house at hee rika soria wii), 1979 July 12-1979 July 13 (Box 3, Item 100)
    - [SHJ-100-A] ~Yagore kütise basa rihoro (Chant prior to start of dance), 1979 July 12-1979 July 13 (Box 3, Item 100)
    - [SHJ-100-A] 2nd Big chant session, 1979 July 12-1979 July 13 (Box 3, Item 100)
    - [SHJ-100-A] Wai Basa (fish dance), 1979 July 12-1979 July 13 (Box 3, Item 100)
    - [SHJ-100-B] Hee (Yurupari flutes at night), 1979 July 12-1979 July 13 (Box 3, Item 100)
    - [SHJ-100-B] ~Waribi keti (Warimi story), 1979 (Box 3, Item 100)
    - [SHJ-101-A] Hee rika sooria wii ~yagore kütise 3 (3rd big chant Session), 1979 July 12-1979 July 13 (Box 3, Item 101)
    - [SHJ-101-B] Hee rika sooria wii ~yagore kütise 3 gaha (3rd big chant Session end), 1979 July 12-1979 July 13 (Box 3, Item 101)
    - [SHJ-101-B] Basase hee (dancing and Yurupary trumpets), 1979 July 12-1979 July 13 (Box 3, Item 101)
    - [SHJ-101-B] Hee rika sooria wii ~yagore kütise 4 (4th big chant Session), 1979 July 12-1979 July 13 (Box 3, Item 101)
    - [SHJ-102-A] Kahi Ekagü (Giving cioca chant session), 1979 July 12-1979 July 13 (Box 3, Item 102)
    - [SHJ-102-B] Kahi Ekagü gaha (Giving coca chant session end), 1979 July 12-1979 July 13 (Box 3, Item 102)
    - [SHJ-102-B] Idire iogü (Chant session pouring-out beer), 1979 July 12-1979 July 13 (Box 3, Item 102)
    - [SHJ-103-A] Idire iogü gaha (Chant session pouring-out beer end), 1979 July 12-1979 July 13 (Box 3, Item 103)
    - [SHJ-103-B] Ayawa ~yabi, sita ~bakara keti(Ayawa get night and earth story), 1979 (Box 3, Item 103)
    - [SHJ-103-B] Gawa gahe~udi keti (story about white peoples' goods, aeroplanes), 1979 (Box 3, Item 103)
    - [SHJ-103-B] Poro Basa keti (about Paul dance millenarian movement), 1979 (Box 3, Item 103)
    - [SHJ-103-B] Gawa ~basa~raka ~keara (White peoples' attacks), 1979 (Box 3, Item 103)
    - [SHJ-103-B] Gawa ~basaraka ~keara 1 (killings and war stories 1), 1979 (Box 3, Item 103)
    - [SHJ-104-A] Yeba keti (Yeba myth), 1979 (Box 3, Item 104)
    - [SHJ-104-B] Yeba keti gaha (Yeba myth end), 1979 (Box 3, Item 104)
    - [SHJ-104-B] Gawa ~basaraka ~keara 2 (killings and war stories 2), 1979 (Box 3, Item 104)
    - [SHJ-105-A] ~Waribi keti (Warimi story), 1979 (Box 3, Item 105)
    - [SHJ-105-B] ~Waribi keti (Warimi story), 1979 (Box 3, Item 105)
    - [SHJ-106-A] ~Waribi, ~riba ~hido keti (Warimi and Poison Anaconda story), 1979 (Box 3, Item 106)
    - [SHJ-106-A] Biahe keti 3 (Chilli-pepper seed story 3), 1979 (Box 3, Item 106)
    - [SHJ-106-B] Biahe keti 4 (Chilli-pepper seed story 4), 1979 (Box 3, Item 106)
    - [SHJ-106-B] Cordoba keti, ~saba Hetaga keti (stories re. relations w. White people), 1979 (Box 3, Item 106)
    - [SHJ-107-A] ~I vida keti 1 (Life history 1), 1979 October 6 (Box 3, Item 107)
    - [SHJ-107-B] ~I vida keti 2 (Life history 2), 1979 October 6 (Box 3, Item 107)
    - [SHJ-108-A] ~I vida keti 3 (Life history 3), 1979 October 6 (Box 3, Item 108)
    - [SHJ-108-B] ~I vida keti 4 (Life history 4), 1979 October 6 (Box 3, Item 108)
    - [SHJ-108-B] Betancure basere gotigü (José Betancur shamanism report), 1979 October 6 (Box 3, Item 108)
    - [SHJ-109-A] Betancure basere gotigü gaha (José Betancur shamanism report end), 1979 October 6 (Box 3, Item 109)
    - [SHJ-109-A] Wahü keti (Wahü story), 1979 (Box 3, Item 109)
    - [SHJ-109-B] Wahü keti gaha (Wahü story end), 1979 (Box 3, Item 109)
    - [SHJ-109-B] Bedise keti (on menstruation), 1979 (Box 3, Item 109)
    - [SHJ-109-B] ~Gaha wati keti (Tinamou spirit story - start of), 1979 (Box 3, Item 109)
    - [SHJ-110-A] ~Kii rükü ~hido hee ~basa hoe~hea wadise (manioc stick anaconda and first people), 1979 (Box 3, Item 110)
    - [SHJ-110-A] Wii ~wadoose rihorohü (talk preceeding house protection shamanism), 1979 (Box 3, Item 110)
    - [SHJ-110-B] Wii ~wadoose (house protection shamanism), 1979 (Box 3, Item 110)
    - [SHJ-110-B] Wii ~wadoose (house protection shamanism), 1979 (Box 3, Item 110)
    - [SHJ-110-B] Wii ~wadoose hüdo gotiro (talk following house divination), 1979 (Box 3, Item 110)
    - [SHJ-111-A] Sawiro, Rika Bü (Sawiro trumpet, piston whistles), 1979 (Box 3, Item 111)
    - [SHJ-111-A] ~Gaha ~wati keti (Tinamou spirit story; info. on language), 1979 (Box 3, Item 111)
    - [SHJ-111-A] ~Wati Bokü keti (White spirit story), 1979 (Box 3, Item 111)
    - [SHJ-111-B] Kii Rükü ~Hido, hee ~basa keti (Manioc-stick anaconda and voyage of ancestors), 1979 (Box 3, Item 111)
    - [SHJ-112-A] ~I ~yariahaü, ~i ~basa keti (History of region and familiy) 1, 1979 (Box 3, Item 112)
    - [SHJ-112-B] ~I ~yariahaü, ~i ~basa keti (History of region and familiy) 2, 1979 (Box 3, Item 112)
    - [SHJ-113-A] ~i ~yariahaü, ~i ~basa keti (History of region and familiy) 3, 1979 (Box 3, Item 113)
    - [SHJ-113-B] ~I ~yariahaü, ~i ~basa keti (History of region and familiy) 4, 1979 (Box 3, Item 113)
    - [SHJ-114-A] ~Kubu ~i buese 1 (How to become a shaman 1), 1979 (Box 3, Item 114)
    - [SHJ-114-B] ~Kubu ~i buese 2 (How to become a shaman 2), 1979 (Box 3, Item 114)
    - [SHJ-115-A] Okayohari besego keti (Okayohari besego Worm and other stories), 1979 (Box 3, Item 115)
    - [SHJ-115-B] Cordoba keti, ~saba Hetaga keti (stories re. killings, war w. Whites 1), 1979 (Box 3, Item 115)
    - [SHJ-115-B] Cordoba keti, ~saba Hetaga keti (stories re. killings, war w. Whites 2), 1979 (Box 3, Item 115)
    - [SHJ-115-B] Garoa keti (People who returned to house of origin (yuhiri wii) story, 1979 (Box 3, Item 115)
    - [SHJ-116-A] Huari wai basere (shamanism for fish caught with barbasco), 1979 (Box 3, Item 116)
    - [SHJ-116-A] Huari wai basere (shamanism for fish caught with barbasco), 1979 (Box 3, Item 116)
    - [SHJ-116-A] Gawa ~basaraka ~keara 1 (killings and war stories 1), 1979 (Box 3, Item 116)
    - [SHJ-116-B] Gawa ~basaraka ~keara 2 (killings and war stories 2), 1979 (Box 3, Item 116)
    - [SHJ-117-A] Ayawa keti (Ayawa story), 1979 (Box 3, Item 117)
    - [SHJ-117-B] Ayawa keti (Ayawa story), 1979 (Box 3, Item 117)
    - [SHJ-118-B] ~Uba ~Wati keti 1 (Uma spirit story 1), 1969 May 25 (Box 3, Item 118)
    - [SHJ-119-A] ~Uba ~Wati keti 2 (Uma spirit story 2), 1979 (Box 3, Item 119)
    - [SHJ-119-B] ~Uba ~Wati keti gaha (Uma spirit story end), 1979 (Box 3, Item 119)
    - [SHJ-120-A] Wai ~Hido keti (Fish Anaconda story), 1979 (Box 3, Item 120)
    - [SHJ-120-A] Kahi ekari oka (Coca handing chant), 1979 (Box 3, Item 120)
    - [SHJ-120-B] Wai ~Hido keti (Fish Anaconda story), 1979 (Box 3, Item 120)
  - Message Hilda -> Mother 08.96; Ika~ra keti
    - [SHJ-098] ~So hakore keti ~koago (Message to mother), 1986 August (Box 3, Item 98)
    - [SHJ-098] ~Wati bokü Keti (white spirit story), 1994 February 21 (Box 3, Item 98)
  - Umero Myths
    - [SHJ-121] ~Basa hoe~hea wadise keti (origin story), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 121)
    - [SHJ-121] Hee ~hido keti (Yurupary anaconda story), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 121)
    - [SHJ-121] ~Robi ~Kubu hee huarudiro keti (Romi Kumu steals yurupary story), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 121)
    - [SHJ-121] Kahi Hako keti (Yagé Mother story), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 121)
    - [SHJ-121] ~Basa hoe~hea wadise gahe~udi keti (anaconda journey; origin of goods), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 121)
    - [SHJ-122] Oa keti (Opossum story), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 122)
    - [SHJ-122] Hee Rika Yai keti, Büho basere (Tree-fruit Jaguar and thunder shamanism), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 122)
    - [SHJ-122] ~Ubüaka Widaü keti (Little sticky man story), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 122)
    - [SHJ-122] ~Kii Rükü ~Hido keti (manioc-stick anaconda story), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 122)
    - [SHJ-122] Guu keti (tortoise story), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 122)
    - [SHJ-123] Wahü keti (Wahü story), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 123)
    - [SHJ-123] ~Paborikü keti (Pamorikü sory, Tatuyo genealogy), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 123)
    - [SHJ-124] Wahü keti (Wahü story), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 124)
    - [SHJ-124] ~Paborikü keti (Pamorikü sory, Tatuyo genealogy), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 124)
    - [SHJ-124] ~Süda ~basa hoe~hea wadise keti (Tatuyo origin story), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 124)
    - [SHJ-124] ~Robi ~kubu hee keti (Romi Kumu steals yurupary), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 124)
    - [SHJ-124]Riatuna hoe~hea wadise (Riatuna origin story), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 124)
    - [SHJ-124] Ayawa oko ~bakar~ra okowu keti (Ayawa look for water story), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 124)
    - [SHJ-124] Güde ~wati keti (Arsehole spirit story), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 124)
    - [SHJ-124] ~kadi ~wati keti (Kani spirit story), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 124)
    - [SHJ-124] Yawira Yuka Keti (Yawira and vultures story), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 124)
    - [SHJ-124] ~Buhi hakü keti (Roofing-leaf father story), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 124)
    - [SHJ-124] ~Wati keti (Myth about spirit), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 124)
    - [SHJ-124] ~Saba hetaga keti gaha (Sama hetaga story contd fr T8B), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Item 124)
    - [SHJ-124] Santa cruz basa (Songs fr. Canto Santa Cruz messianic movement), 1980/1989 (Box 3, Item 124)
- Open Reel Audiotapes
  - Myth
    Housed in LSF container B
    - [2019_0251_0001_01_ac.mp3] ~Kii Rükü ~Hido keti (Manioc Anaconda story), 1970 (Box 4, Item 61)
    - [2019_0251_0001_01_ac.mp3] ~Waribi keti (Warimi story - part of), 1970 (Box 4, Item 61)
    - [2019_0251_0001_02_ac.mp3] Ewa Yai keti (Magic Jaguar and Thunder story, ), 1970 (Box 4, Item 61)
    - [2019_0251_0001_02_ac.mp3] ~Uba ~Wati keti, Wai ~Hido keti (~Uba Spirit and Fish Anaconda story), 1970 (Box 4, Item 61)
    - [2019_0251_0001_02_ac.mp3] Ayawa keti (Ayawa story - part of), 1970 (Box 4, Item 61)
    - [2019_0251_0001_02_ac.mp3] ~Wati Biru keti (Biru Spirit story) Contd. T2G, 1970 (Box 4, Item 61)
    - [2019_0251_0002_01_ac.mp3] ~Wati Biru keti (Biru Spirit story) Contd fr. T1R, 1970 (Box 4, Item 62)
    - [2019_0251_0002_01_ac.mp3] Yeba keti (Yeba story), 1970 (Box 4, Item 62)
    - [2019_0251_0002_01_ac.mp3] Kawia keti (Crab story), 1970 (Box 4, Item 62)
    - [2019_0251_0002_01_ac.mp3] ~Wati Bokü keti (White Spirit story), 1970 (Box 4, Item 62)
    - [2019_0251_0002_01_ac.mp3] Coming of 1st people esp. üko ~hido (Medicine Anaconda), 1970 (Box 4, Item 62)
    - [2019_0251_0002_01_ac.mp3] ~Yukabadahiro keti (Insect story), 1970 (Box 4, Item 62)
    - [2019_0251_0002_01_ac.mp3] Bükü~ra yaiya, yesea keti (Ancient Jaguars and peccaries story), 1970 (Box 4, Item 62)
    - [2019_0251_0002_02_ac.mp3] Õpeo ~wati keti (Spirit-w.Big-Tits story), 1970 (Box 4, Item 62)
    - [2019_0251_0002_02_ac.mp3] ~Wati Güde ~Bagü keti (Spirit-w'out-Anus story), 1970 (Box 4, Item 62)
    - [2019_0251_0002_02_ac.mp3] ~Watia keti (Spirits killed v. chilli smoke story), 1970 (Box 4, Item 62)
    - [2019_0251_0002_02_ac.mp3] Wahü keti (Rubber Fruit Man story), 1970 (Box 4, Item 62)
    - [2019_0251_0002_02_ac.mp3] Yeba Bühü keti (Yeba, spider and barkcloth aprons story), 1970 (Box 4, Item 62)
    - [2019_0251_0002_02_ac.mp3] Yeba keti (Yeba story - meeting w. Wai ~Hido/Fish Anaconda), 1970 (Box 4, Item 62)
    - [2019_0251_0003_01_ac.mp3] Arrival of Barasana sibs, ~Robi ~Kubu and Hee ~Basa ('Yuruparí People'), 1970 (Box 4, Item 63)
    - [2019_0251_0003_01_ac.mp3] Sticky People in Ewüra Wii and Eye Eater Spirit, 1970 (Box 4, Item 63)
    - [2019_0251_0003_01_ac.mp3] ~Waribi, ~Aya Hako keti (Warimi and Snake Mother story), 1970 (Box 4, Item 63)
    - [2019_0251_0003_01_ac.mp3] ~Waribi ~Rabe ~Riba ~Riba ~Hido keti (Warimi, Rame and Poison Anaconda story - cont. of previous item), 1970 (Box 4, Item 63)
    - [2019_0251_0003_01_ac.mp3] ~Uyuyokoroa keti (~Uyuyokoroa story - contd. on T3R), 1970 (Box 4, Item 63)
    - [2019_0251_0003_02_ac.mp3] ~Uyuyokoroa keti (~Uyuyokoroa story - contd. Fr. T3G), 1970 (Box 4, Item 63)
    - [2019_0251_0003_02_ac.mp3] Ga ~Basa Bagü keti (Cannibal Eagle story), 1970 (Box 4, Item 63)
    - [2019_0251_0003_02_ac.mp3] ~Basü and Yai keti (Man and Jaguar story), 1970 (Box 4, Item 63)
    - [2019_0251_0003_02_ac.mp3] ~Kii Rükü ~Hido keti (Manioc Anaconda story), 1970 (Box 4, Item 63)
    - [2019_0251_0004_01_ac.mp3] Ayawa keti, ~Waribi keti (Ayawa and Warimi story - contd on T4R), undated (Box 4, Item 64)
    - [2019_0251_0004_02_ac.mp3] ~Waribi keti (Warimi story - contd fr. T4G), undated (Box 4, Item 64)
    - [2019_0251_0009_01_ac.mp3] Ayawa keti, Waribi keti (Ayawa and Warimi story), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_01_ac.mp3] Yeba keti (Yeba story), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_01_ac.mp3] Yeba keti (Yeba story), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_01_ac.mp3] ~Wati Bokü keti (White Spirit story), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_01_ac.mp3] Gu, Yai keti (Tortoise and Jaguar story), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_01_ac.mp3] ~Yokoago keti (Falling Star story), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_01_ac.mp3] Gu ~kihiika keti (Tiny Tortoise story), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_01_ac.mp3] Buo keti (Agouti Woman in the underworld story), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_01_ac.mp3] ~Kii Rükü ~Hido keti (Manioc Anaconda story), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_01_ac.mp3] ~Aya Hako keti (Snake Mother story), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_01_ac.mp3] Busuri ~Yoko keti (Morning Venus story), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_01_ac.mp3] ~Uba ~Wati keti (~Uba Spirit story - part of), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_01_ac.mp3] ~Baka ~Yaba keti (Patio Deer story - contd. On T10R), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_02_ac.mp3] ~Baka ~Yaba keti (Patio Deer story - contd. fr T10G), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_02_ac.mp3] ~Waribi keti (Warimi story), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_02_ac.mp3] ~Buhihu keti (Moon's incest story), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_02_ac.mp3] ~Buhihu keti (Moon eating bones story), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_02_ac.mp3] Creation of people (Warimi?), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_02_ac.mp3] ~Gaseroa, ~Goha keti (Cockroach and ~goha frog story), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_02_ac.mp3] Yeba keti (Yeba story), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_02_ac.mp3] Wekü keti (Tapir story), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_02_ac.mp3] ~Wati Güde ~Bagü keti (Spirit-w'out-Anus story), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0009_02_ac.mp3] ~Waribi, ~Rabe keti (Story of Warimi and Rame), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0010_01_ac.mp3] ~Waribi, ~Rabe keti (Story of Warimi and Rame), undated (Box 5, Item 70)
    - [2019_0251_0011_01_ac.mp3] Yeba keti (Yeba story), undated (Box 5, Item 71)
    - [2019_0251_0011_01_ac.mp3] ~Buhi Hakü keti Owner of Roofing Leaves story), undated (Box 5, Item 71)
    - [2019_0251_0012_01_ac.mp3]~Uba ~Wati keti (~Uba Spirit story - contd. Fr T14), undated (Box 5, Item 72)
    - [2019_0251_0012_01_ac.mp3] ~Baka ~Yaba keti (Patio Deer story), undated (Box 5, Item 72)
    - [2019_0251_0012_01_ac.mp3] ~Waribi keti (Warimi story), undated (Box 5, Item 72)
    - [2019_0251_0013_01_ac.mp3] Play story, undated (Box 5, Item 73)
    - [2019_0251_0013_01_ac.mp3] Yeba keti (Yeba story), undated (Box 5, Item 73)
    - [2019_0251_0013_01_ac.mp3] Yeba keti (Yeba story), undated (Box 5, Item 73)
    - [2019_0251_0013_01_ac.mp3] ~Wati Bokü keti (White Spirit story), undated (Box 5, Item 73)
    - [2019_0251_0013_01_ac.mp3] ~Wati Güde ~Bagü keti (Spirit-w'out-Anus story), undated (Box 5, Item 73)
    - [2019_0251_0013_02_ac.mp3] Gu, Yai keti (Tortoise and Jaguar story), undated (Box 5, Item 73)
    - [2019_0251_0013_02_ac.mp3] ~Yokoago keti (Falling Star story), undated (Box 5, Item 73)
    - [2019_0251_0013_02_ac.mp3] Gu ~kihiika keti (Tiny Tortoise story), undated (Box 5, Item 73)
    - [2019_0251_0013_02_ac.mp3] Buo keti (Agouti Woman in the underworld story), undated (Box 5, Item 73)
    - [2019_0251_0013_02_ac.mp3] ~Kii Rükü ~Hido keti (Manioc Anaconda story), undated (Box 5, Item 73)
    - [2019_0251_0013_02_ac.mp3] ~Aya Hako keti (Snake Mother story), undated (Box 5, Item 73)
    - [2019_0251_0013_02_ac.mp3] Busuri ~Yoko keti (Morning Venus story), undated (Box 5, Item 73)
    - [2019_0251_0013_02_ac.mp3] ~Uba ~Wati keti (~Uba Spirit story - contd. on T13), undated (Box 5, Item 73)
    - [2019_0251_0014_01_ac.mp3] Yeba keti (Yeba story), undated (Box 5, Item 74)
    - [2019_0251_0014_01_ac.mp3] Yeba keti (Yeba story) and commentary, undated (Box 5, Item 74)
    - [2019_0251_0014_01_ac.mp3] ~Buhihu keti (Sun and Moon story); account f cosmolgy, weather, eclipses, undated (Box 5, Item 74)
    - [2019_0251_0015_01_ac.mp3] ~Waribi keti (Warimi story), undated (Box 6, Item 75)
    - [2019_0251_0015_01_ac.mp3] Hea Güso keti (Origin of Fire story), undated (Box 6, Item 75)
    - [2019_0251_0015_01_ac.mp3] Ayawa keti (Ayawa story - part of), undated (Box 6, Item 75)
    - [2019_0251_0015_01_ac.mp3] ~Robi ~Kubu keti (Romi Kumu story), undated (Box 6, Item 75)
    - [2019_0251_0015_01_ac.mp3] ~Beka ~Bidi keti (Antbird story), undated (Box 6, Item 75)
    - [2019_0251_0015_01_ac.mp3] ~Kode, ~Yasa keti (Woodpecker and kingfisher story), undated (Box 6, Item 75)
    - [2019_0251_0015_01_ac.mp3] ~Wati keti (Spirit who feeds odd parts of body story), undated (Box 6, Item 75)
    - [2019_0251_0015_01_ac.mp3] ~Uba ~Wati keti (~Uba Spirit story - part of), undated (Box 6, Item 75)
    - [2019_0251_0017_01_ac.mp3] ~Buhihu keti (Moon's incest story), undated (Box 6, Item 77)
    - [2019_0251_0017_01_ac.mp3] ~Buhihu keti (Moon eating bones story), undated (Box 6, Item 77)
    - [2019_0251_0017_01_ac.mp3] ~Basa ruhease keti (Creation of people story), undated (Box 6, Item 77)
    - [2019_0251_0017_01_ac.mp3] ~Gaseroa, ~Goha keti (Cockroach and ~goha frog story), undated (Box 6, Item 77)
    - [2019_0251_0017_01_ac.mp3] Yeba keti (Yeba story), undated (Box 6, Item 77)
    - [2019_0251_0018_01_ac.mp3] Untitled, undated (Box 6, Item 78)
    - [2019_0251_0018_01_ac.mp3] ~Wati Güde ~Bagü keti (Spirit-w'out-Anus story), undated (Box 6, Item 78)
    - [2019_0251_0019_01_ac.mp3] ~Robi ~Kubu keti (Romi Kumu story), undated (Box 6, Item 79)
    - [2019_0251_0019_01_ac.mp3] ~Watia keti (Spirit and butterfly; spirit in hole stories), undated (Box 6, Item 79)
    - [2019_0251_0019_01_ac.mp3] ~Wati keti (Spirit and tinamou meat gifts story), undated (Box 6, Item 79)
    - [2019_0251_0019_01_ac.mp3] ~Robi ~Kubu keti (Romi Kumu story), undated (Box 6, Item 79)
    - [2019_0251_0021_01_ac.mp3] üko ~Hido keti (Medicine Anaconda story), undated (Box 7, Item 81)
    - [2019_0251_0021_01_ac.mp3] Gu, Yai keti (Tortoise and Jaguar story), undated (Box 7, Item 81)
    - [2019_0251_0021_01_ac.mp3] Gu ~kihiika keti (Tiny Tortoise story), undated (Box 7, Item 81)
    - [2019_0251_0021_01_ac.mp3] ~Yokoago keti (Falling Star story), undated (Box 7, Item 81)
    - [2019_0251_0021_01_ac.mp3] ~Gohao keti (Goha frog story), undated (Box 7, Item 81)